[Music]
good day everyone my name
is director for prudential thank you hrc
award for the nominations an award that
has been given to prudential this is the
second year we received this award with
proud our team for this year is about
preparing our people for the future of
work and skills
we put our effort to focus on upskilling
re-skilling engaging and retaining our
talent this award is a symbol of our
achievement and another milestone to
build prudential to be the home for best
people
i dedicate this award to all having
influential the management of prudential
and to all employees influential big
congratulations
to all of us
you